

Emin Imanverdiyev

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Date of birth: 15 October 2003

Place of birth: Azerbaijan, Lerik

Nationality: Azerbaijani

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am an Full Stack Developer with 2+ years in the software development industry. I have strong knowledge of multiple web development languages such as HTML5, CSS3,SCSS, JavaScript, React Js (Vite Js), Bootstrap and jQuery. My expertise also includes back-end technologies such as C# and MS SQL. I have a passion for creating clean and efficient code that meets user requirements while ensuring scalability for future growth. My strongest qualities are my attention to detail and problem-solving skills.

EXPERIENCE

September 2023 - February 2024

Full-stcak Developer

DigitalHands MMC / Azerbaijan, Baku

We work as a team every day. We complete the given projects by the deadline. We discuss the errors in the project as a group. Our work so far includes Agency Website , Archeticture , Psychology and more. Use next developer technologies: React js , C#, ORM , RESTful APIs, Ms Sql , Git , Github , Bootstrap, HTML , Css

June 2022 - July 2022

Front End Developer (Intern)

URcompany / Azerbaijan, Baku

We coded a project for a new company. The front is mine. I coded the front part using HTML CSS JS technologies.

EDUCATION

2021 - Now

Bachelor of Education (BEd)

Azerbaijan Oil and Industry University / Azerbaijan, Baku

From the first semester I started at university, they taught C++ programming. Algorithm tasks, data structures, etc. I started learning. Then I learned the basic knowledge and syntax of the C# programming language.

SKILLS

Expert	CSS	Expert	HTML
Experienced	Jquery	Experienced	JavaScript
Experienced	Bootstrap	Experienced	React.js
Skillful	T-SQL	Experienced	MS SQL

+994515888968

emin.imanverdiyevv@gmail.com

 Azerbaijan, Baku, Yeni Guneshli , D massiv , Building 9, Apartment 116, AZ1133

LINKS

- (in) imanverdlev
- (n) imanverdlev

LANGUAGES

Azerbaijan - Native

English - Intermediate

Russian - Beginner

Turkish - Intermediate

Git	Expert	RESTful APIs	Expert
c#	Experienced	.NET	Experienced
Entity Framework	Skillful	SOLID	Experienced
MVC	Experienced	JSON	Experienced
Figma	Expert	Github	Experienced
SASS	Expert		

PROJECTS

September 2023 - October 2023

Agency Website

Azerbaijan, Baku

Part of Project Front belongs to me. The front end part is written with react js. The backend is written in java. We integrated as a team. When a problem arose, we solved it as a group.

• June 2023 - June 2023

Weather App

Azerbaijan, Baku

I only wrote the front part of this project using $\mathsf{HTML}\,\textsc{,}\,\mathsf{SASS}\,\textsc{,}\,\mathsf{JS}$

November 2023 - November 2023

Architecture and Design

Azerbaijan, Baku

I only coded the backend part of this project using the c# programming language. I use the REST API.

• June 2023 - June 2023

URcompany

Azerbaijan, Baku

Part of Project Front belongs to me. The front end part is written with JS. The backend is written in java. We integrated as a team.

• May 2023 - May 2023

MilliTech Company

Azerbaijan, Baku

I used different technologies in this project. For example HTML CSS JS JQUERY BOOTSTRAP etc